Subtitles are color-coded by country,
and this setting cannot be changed.
Unlock.
You've got to unlock your feet.
-Don't rush it.
-Do it slowly.
Oh no. Be careful.
Team Türkiye's in a bad spot.
The one on his left has lost balance.
She's losing it. Keep it together.
It was really tough.
I was at my absolute limit.
It started with my fingers going numb.
I had to squeeze out
every ounce of strength to stay on.
Hang in there!
Hang in there, Nonoka.
-Hang in there, that's it.
-Come on. You can last longer than this!
Stay strong. I know you have it in you.
Hang in there!
Stay on just a little longer. Focus!
Come on! We're counting on you!
You got this!
Hang in there, Nonoka.
That's all right.
-Good job.
-Good effort.
-You did your best.
-Yeah, well done.
I'm so sorry.
As soon as I unlocked my feet,
all the exhaustion that had built up
in my legs hit me instantly,
and I fell off
before I could even put up a fight.
Don't look at her. Stay focused, buddy!
-Keep going, Anıl.
-Keep going!
That's it, just copy Team Mongolia.
Anıl, this is
exactly what Team Mongolia did.
Yes, Anıl, that's it.
There you go, find your balance.
-Looking great.
-Yeah.
He's balancing
almost entirely on his left leg.
Straighten your right leg
and bend your left slightly.
Straighten your right leg.
That's what he's doing.
Perfect form.
You're a chameleon,
mirroring his every move.
They're giving away all my tricks to him.
Nice pose, man.
It's your job. I need to cheat.
Let's do it, man.
Fifty minutes.
Amazing.
You're killing it!
Sixty minutes.
-Bravo.
Well done!
Eighty minutes.
Great job, Lkhagva-Ochir.
Amazing balance.
100 minutes.
You're doing great.
I'm doing great, right?
I knew it was going to be
a long and painful stretch up there.
And sure enough,
I was starting to feel it in my thighs.
In order to reduce that fatigue,
I came up with a new
resting pose every minute.
I alternated between three or four poses.
That way, I could give my legs a break.
He's good. He's sticking it out.
You're the best. No one even comes close!
It's too easy.
Is he doing that on purpose
or is he gassed out?
He's gassed out.
He's giving his muscles a break.
In Çanakkale stands the Mirror Bazaar
Mother, I set forth against the enemy
I sang to motivate myself.
I sang "Çanakkale Türküsü," for example.
That's how I stayed locked in.
I'm staying here
till I either die or pass out.
The Turkish player's found his sweet spot.
Wow, he's quite impressive too.
-They're going to be there all night.
-They've practically settled in.
It'd be nice if he accidentally grabbed
the ring with both hands.
Yeah, I wish he'd forget where he was
and grab it without thinking.
Right, without realizing.
I was going numb from lack of blood flow.
I had pins and needles
and numbness in my hands.
He's getting pins and needles.
He's not looking too well right now.
Anıl, Mongolia's struggling.
His face looks awful.
Lkhagva-Ochir, you've got to hold on.
I focused only on myself.
My hands and feet were cold as ice.
It was like my spirit had left my body.
It was excruciating,
but giving up isn't an option for me.
You got this.
Didn't his hand just touch the ring?
-He almost grabbed the ring, right?
-Yeah.
That's exactly what we were hoping
Team Mongolia would do.
-Come on, Mongolia, fall off already.
-I wish he'd just give up.
Come on, put your hand in there.
I'm not going to lie, it was tough.
But if I gave up,
I'd never be able to live it down.
That's what I told myself then.
Türkiye's suffering too.
-Hang in there, man.
-Hold it!
Don't give up.
Don't give up. Keep holding on!
I'm going to stay here till I pass out.
His hand, his hand! He touched it.
He touched it.
Didn't he just touch it?
His hand, his hand! He touched it.
-Wait, wait. Don't move.
-Don't move.
He grabbed the ring.
-Did he touch it?
-Yeah, he did.
DISQUALIFIED FOR TWO HANDS ON A HANDHOLD
Game over.
I showed them
how strong we Mongolians are.
This win means
all three teams are tied now,
so we were all ecstatic.
I was devastated to lose like that.
As I was shifting my pose
to ease the strain,
my hand touched the ring briefly,
but I removed it right away.
I let my guard down in that moment.
I let my teammates down badly.
That wasn't how it was supposed to end.
It shouldn't have ended like that.
You fought well, my friend.
TIED FOR 1ST: 4 POINTS
We need Team Mongolia to come in second.
Yeah, we need them to come in second.
If we come in first and Team Japan last,
then Japan's out of the competition
right away.
Team Mongolia was doing really well.
At the very least,
we had to beat Team Japan.
If we were to come in third place,
there'd be nothing we could do
because we'd be eliminated.
First, we have to beat Japan.
Then we'll tackle Mongolia,
one step at a time.
The worst-case scenario
is Team Türkiye winning this.
We knew we were on shaky ground.
Since we didn't know
our ranking for the second game,
the only way to guarantee our survival
was to beat Türkiye.
It's no longer about
catching up to Team Mongolia,
but about beating Team Türkiye.
Our elimination is on the line, after all.
So the pressure is off the charts.
The team rep match of Physical: Asia.
The representative from each country
participating in the sack toss match,
please make your way to the arena.
-Ogeday!
-Go, Ogeday!
OGEDAY
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM ROWER
That's our rower!
-Itoi!
-Let's go!
-You got this!
Warriors.
-Mount up!
Don't stress it, man.
Those two have nothing on you.
In the sack toss match,
you must toss the sack
that comes into your zone
over to the next opponent's zone.
Damn, so it's all about stamina.
Orkhonbayar has the upper hand here.
Mongolian wrestlers
undergo intensive strength training.
We grow up wrestling horses,
so I've got a solid grip.
Looking at who he's up against,
I'm confident Ogeday will win this.
He was a national team rower for Türkiye,
and he has incredible muscular endurance.
I needed to aim for first place.
That's all I was focused on.
This game was made for me.
As part of my baseball training,
I trained extensively with a kettlebell.
I've also thrown countless pitches,
so I'm pumped to flex my skills.
This will totally be
a strength match against Türkiye.
We can win this.
SACK TOSS ORDER DRAW
What number did you get?
-Yes!
ORKHONBAYAR, OGEDAY, YOSHIO
-Itoi, stay calm and focused.
-Okay.
All right. Let's have fun.
I'm confident.
Anıl, you hold your breath
when you're lifting, right?
Remind me to hold my breath
because that's the key here.
Okay, I'll cue your breaths.
The fourth game of the team rep match.
Sack toss match.
Once the whistle blows,
the match will begin.
Stand by.
Ready…
PHYSICAL: ASIA
8. FORMIDABLE FOE
Ready…
-Good throw, good throw.
-Good job.
It was light.
There you go. Now, control your breathing.
-That's it.
-Amazing.
-Push it up. Yes, that's it!
-Nice! So easy.
-Just like that, Ogeday!
-Too easy.
The first throw went well.
It was a lot easier than I expected.
Stay calm.
It's going to be a miss.
-Nice.
-Nice and high.
Your throw was the highest.
My teammates cheered me on,
saying my throw was the highest.
It felt good.
-He won't last.
-Yeah, he'll tire himself out like that.
Watch out, watch out.
Careful.
Nice, he missed.
You have plenty of time.
-Nice!
-Nicely done.
You don't want to miss twice.
The first contestant to make
the most mistakes was bound to lose,
so we were all very nervous.
Control your breathing.
-That's it.
-That was beautiful.
-A piece of cake!
-Perfect.
There's no rush. Take your time.
Great throw.
-Damn.
-Go again.
-Keep your cool.
-You still have 20 seconds!
-Damn.
-Go again.
-Keep your cool.
-You still have 20 seconds!
You still have 20 seconds!
-You nailed it!
-There it is.
-Good job!
-That went high.
My heart was thumping out of my chest.
Based on his background and body weight,
Team Mongolia had the upper hand.
But this is Physical: Asia.
You never know
what's going to happen here.
Nefise, this is going to last a while.
It's fun though.
Having fun is what matters most.
It makes you unbeatable.
I kept my mind focused
on the accuracy of the first throw.
That's right!
-Too easy.
-That was the best one yet.
That was the best so far.
All those pitches
from his baseball days must help.
It's insane how focused he is
on every throw.
I know, right?
He's doing too well.
He's even better than Team Mongolia.
The weight of the sack
will now be increased.
The ball's getting heavier.
Stand by.
-Yes, right there.
-Looking good!
Yes, that was effortless.
Love it, Orkhonbayar!
-Let's go, Ogeday!
-The closer you are, the better.
-Don't forget your hips!
-Looking good. Control your breathing.
Your hips!
-Well done.
-Good job!
-He almost missed it.
-All right!
-He's struggling!
-He's fading.
All right, Itoi. Let's get it in one go.
-Look at it go effortlessly!
-That was effortless!
Too easy!
The increased weight
wasn't an issue for me yet.
All right.
Nice, that was a perfect throw.
Don't lift it, drag it!
He's dragging it along.
Maybe he can't handle the weight.
Throw it.
-Amazing.
-Bravo!
He really struggled to get that one over.
-He barely made it.
-Yeah.
He's hanging by a thread.
-Watch your breathing and hips.
-Hips!
-Yes!
-All right.
I bet he's sweating it now.
-There's still time.
-No rush, you still have 20 seconds.
Don't panic! There's still time!
One more miss, and it's over.
-Nice, that's it.
-Bravo.
-Keep doing that.
-Very nice.
I can afford one mistake.
-That's right. The other guy missed too.
-No problem.
-Nice!
Control your breathing
and use your hips to let go quickly.
There you go.
-Get closer!
-You're standing at an angle.
Turn fully around.
-Get closer!
-You're standing at an angle.
Turn fully around.
Relax, there's still time.
Well done.
-Nice!
-Bravo.
-That barely made it over.
-He's barely making it.
I think he's got
less than ten throws left in him.
You were standing at an angle.
Next time, turn fully around.
Got it. Keep the tips coming.
Get into position and turn fully around.
-Control your breathing.
-Get the angle right.
Use those hips to power through.
The hips.
Yes, that's it!
Control your breathing and use your hips!
Bravo!
-Bravo!
-Beautiful!
Sure, sometimes I mess up my throws.
But I'm going to keep swinging
till I drop.
-You're killing it, champ!
-Great throw!
I bet you can last all night!
I'll make it last all night.
Easy money!
-I think he's got the hang of it now.
-Yeah.
He's got the technique down.
He counts to three as he throws.
He's adjusting his stance
and making some tweaks.
The Turkish player had a rough start
with lots of misses,
but he kept pulling through just in time.
It was incredible how he did that.
It's all right.
-It's all good.
-You got this.
Nice guns, Itoi.
Cannonball shoulders!
-Up!
-Nailed it!
Nice, nice. Easy.
We've got this in the bag.
-Great throw!
-Nailed it as usual!
You're standing at an angle, Ogeday.
The others are gassed out.
-Look at how high that went!
-He's got energy to spare!
Up!
-You got it!
-Great throw, Orkhonbayar!
Let's go, champ. That's it.
Bravo!
-High!
-All right!
Bring it!
They'll be going forever at this weight.
It's going to last a while.
All right!
Yes, here we go.
This will make it harder
for the other two.
This is the real deal now.
-Use this time to rest.
-Breathe.
Rest up, rest up.
The weight of the sack
-will now be increased.
-Up?
You're throwing higher,
so Team Türkiye is going to struggle.
Stand by.
-Up!
-Too easy.
-Nice!
All right.
-He does it so easily.
-Yeah, he makes it look so light.
He throws so fast.
That guy gets better
as the weight gets heavier.
-Tighten those glutes.
-The glutes!
Great job.
Good.
-That was too close.
-Team Türkiye's cutting it close.
He almost didn't make it.
Let's go.
Lock in and focus. Up!
All right!
That's it, with height to spare!
You're doing great, Itoi.
He's wasting energy
by throwing it so high.
He's exerting himself a lot more than you.
-Looking good.
-Up!
Up!
-Yeah!
-That's it!
Man, "That's it!"
Come on, Ogeday!
The other guy's gassed out.
Don't forget to tighten those glutes.
-Tense those glutes.
-Up!
That's it!
Damn, he barely managed to get it over.
-It went over like this.
-He barely got it over.
All right, all right!
If you can, throw it to the far side
and make it harder for Japan.
We need to beat Japan.
Let's send them home.
It doesn't matter how he gets it over.
One country will be eliminated
after this game.
That's what made it so nerve-racking.
-All right!
Good one!
-Tighten those glutes!
-Up!
Yes!
-Yeah!
-Yes!
He's nervous.
Don't stress, there's still time.
He's in trouble.
Don't rush it. You have 15 seconds.
Breathe.
Tense the glutes!
He's nervous.
Team Türkiye's finished.
-Come on, one more!
-Keep your cool!
No way. Is it over for us?
Don't panic now. You have five seconds.
Five, four, three, two…
-Yes!
Hey, you and the Japanese guy
are totally going to beat Türkiye.
-Throw it high!
-Nice! Easy.
-Good throw.
-That one was perfect!
You're the best here, Orkhonbayar.
Does that guy ever miss?
Please throw it a bit farther out.
-It's okay. Don't panic.
-It's okay.
Let's go again.
He missed.
Try to get it a bit higher.
The entire team was on edge.
It was impossible to stand or sit still.
Well, any front-runner could fall behind.
I've seen it happen
in previous seasons too.
That's just the nature of sports.
Great form!
Again? Seriously?
I hope they increase the weight.
The time limit will now be reduced
to 15 seconds.
The time limit's been reduced
to 15 seconds!
-Fifteen seconds.
-No problem.
Orkhonbayar,
swing from the top like this, okay?
Don't mess up.
One mistake and we're done for.
This would work to my advantage.
It was taking me
around ten seconds to get it over,
while the other two were taking around 15.
-One miss, and it's over, right?
-Fifteen seconds.
You only get one shot now.
You can't slip up!
-You've got this.
-Come on, Itoi!
Stand by.
-All right!
-Up!
-That only took four seconds.
-He got that over in four seconds.
-Easy!
-Great work!
I thought I'd speed things up a bit.
-Let's go, champ!
-Give it some juice!
-Nice.
-Bravo!
-Don't rush it.
-Let's go!
Focus and up!
-Was that too close?
-Yes, a bit.
All we need is one miss.
Nice.
He's stepped it up.
He's exhausted but won't give up, huh?
If he loses, that's it for the team.
This is truly their last chance.
Come on, please fail!
One miss is all we need.
All right, all right.
He almost missed that one, Ogeday.
I saw.
He's shaking out his arms. They're shot.
Yeah, his arms are shot.
The longer it drags on,
the better it is for us.
He only has to miss one throw.
-One miss, and it's over.
-Exactly.
This entire game depends on
just one opponent missing a throw.
We're going to hold out
until Japan slips up.
That's the spot.
Big thrust up!
-Chuck it up high!
-Up!
Come on. Come on.
-Nice!
-Good job.
Once again, he got it over by a hair.
I was screaming inside.
My nerves were more shot than his by then.
He sure is persistent.
-Don't worry about what he's doing.
-Go, Itoi!
Please slip up just once.
Just a slip of the hand.
He'll panic if he makes a mistake.
-One miss, and he'll be fumbling.
-Right.
Let's go!
You got this. Watch your legs.
It's okay, go again. Don't rush.
Yes!
-Come on, please panic!
-One more miss!
You got this. Keep your cool!
It was very stressful
because the clock was ticking.
Keep your cool!
All right!
-Nice work.
-Very nice.
Let's keep that pace.
Damn!
He's starting to slip up!
Just keep doing what you're doing!
-I told you we're the most solid.
-Very nice!
Push through with your hips!
-Bravo.
-Bravo!
It's going to be ten seconds now.
Is it getting heavier?
The weight of the sack
will now be increased.
It's gotten heavier.
-You okay?
-Orkhonbayar!
I'm fine.
I'll win this without a problem.
You only have one chance, okay?
You've got to get it in one go.
This is a battle against myself.
Regardless,
I won't quit because
you never know what will happen.
I'm going to keep throwing for my team.
You've got this, Itoi.
Your throws are the highest.
-All right.
-Swing!
-Amazing!
-What a throw!
Team Mongolia's throws
aren't as high as before.
He's cutting it close.
Find your position.
Engage your glutes, breathe, and throw!
Yeah!
He's cutting it very close.
Let's go, Itoi!
-Let's go!
-Focus.
Just like last time.
-Nice!
All right! You crushed that one.
Keep going as you were.
Just keep at it, Ogeday!
Find your footprints.
Glutes.
Give it a hard thrust!
Throw it up!
-Bravo!
-Bravo! Keep at it.
Damn, that barely made it over again.
Come on, Itoi. Hang in there.
All right, focus.
-Let's go!
-Keep your focus.
He's going to miss, he's going to miss.
His throws are getting lower.
Just keep at it!
You're doing good.
Come on, champ. You found the footprints.
Please slip.
Fire up your glutes.
-Yes!
-That's it!
-That barely made it.
-I know, it was so close.
It just went on and on.
I wondered how long
we'd have to keep this up.
Itoi, it's now a game of patience.
Come on!
-Let's go!
-Keep going. Focus!
-Nailed it!
-You're doing too good.
I was running on fumes by then,
but I clenched my teeth and kept pushing.
I would've done a thousand more throws
if that's what it took.
You've got to nail the first swing.
Swing and go!
I had no doubt I'd get it over.
-Up!
Go, Ogeday!
His throws have gotten lower.
Stick with what you're doing.
All you have to do is get it over.
It doesn't matter how.
-He found his footprints.
-Let's go, Ogeday!
That's the spot. Glutes.
Look up!
Yeah!
-This is it!
-Three, one…
Five seconds.
-Great work! You did well.
-Good work!
Ogeday tried his best.
He'd been throwing down there
for an hour and a half.
I feel awful for knocking
my team out of the competition.
It breaks my heart
that we lost because of me.
Ogeday truly gave his all to the very end.
I thank him for his efforts.
-It's all right. Great work.
-You did amazing.
It's over!
MONGOLIA AND JAPAN SAFE FROM ELIMINATION
That was the moment our team
secured our advancement to the next quest.
Itoi ignited a spark in Team Japan.
There's more to come
because we have yet to hit
the heights of the Tokyo Dome.
The totem hold match.
We're in the top four now.
We'll topple the others
and be the first to make the top three.
Yes!
GROUP B FINAL RESULTS
The third quest
of Physical: Asia has ended.
Team Türkiye has been eliminated
from Physical: Asia.
Each team member
will now destroy their torso.
Our aim was to leave here as the victors.
As I said in the beginning,
we didn't come here for fun.
-We are Turkish!
-We are strong!
-We are ready!
We were full of confidence.
We didn't doubt for a second
that we'd reach the finals.
Come on, Nefise!
Hang in there. This is nothing.
We proved that Türkiye
was the top contender in this competition.
It was truly an honor
to compete alongside you all.
You all gave your very best,
and I'm grateful
to have had you by my side.
Here we go.
In the name of Allah.
This is brutal.
It was a unique experience
and an honorable, gritty fight.
It was amazing, and I had a blast.
It was an honor to fight shoulder
to shoulder with my team to the end.
We showed
that we are a fearless, strong team.
The pride of having been part of that
is enough for me.
I think we created
some great stories here.
We did ourselves and our country proud.
Our story ends here,
and now, it's our turn
to catch a flight home.
I'm very sad.
Our honor and pride
have taken a real beating.
But we truly gave it our all.
Can you please stop watching
at the end of the second quest?
Sending kisses to everyone.
I'm thrilled and proud to have been
a member of Team Türkiye.
-One, two, three, Türkiye!
Our team really came together
like a family.
Thanks to my awesome teammates.
You all did a great job.
As for the rest of you,
the competition will be a lot easier
now that we're out of the picture.
Good luck.
May the strongest team win.
PHYSICAL: ASIA
-So many less people, man.
-All the flags are still here.
And we're down to four.
-The final four.
-Four remain.
They did it.
-Welcome.
-Hi.
Nice to see you all again.
It feels strange
with only four teams left.
I know, like we're missing something.
Well, there are a lot fewer of us now.
Who will we go up against next?
It's all the same now.
We have to fight to the death regardless.
Half the contestants were gone,
but the room didn't feel too empty to me.
I wanted it to be emptier.
In fact, I couldn't wait
to kick the rest of them
out of the competition.
Should we send Team Japan
or Team Mongolia home next?
It doesn't really matter
-as long as we stay in.
-I do want Team Australia eliminated.
Yeah, that would be nice.
But they're just too strong.
Team Australia is indeed strong.
I'm as confident as ever.
Physically, there is no one
that can beat us.
I'm still clutching out
that they start bringing in
wrestling mats.
-Rob's so eager to fight.
-By God!
Physical: Asia.
-Physical: Asia.
-I wonder what's in store for us now.
The all-seeing eye.
Of the eight countries,
four have survived.
Australia.
The Republic of Korea.
Mongolia.
Japan.
Congratulations, everybody.
Nailed it.
Prior to the fourth quest,
we will reveal the results
of the pre-quest survey.
The survey.
You know, the question they asked us.
Oh, it's like a poll.
Oh, shoot.
Which contestant do you want to avoid
in a one-on-one match?
Who do I not want to go up against?
This is hard.
Do I have to say I'm afraid of them?
I'm trying to think.
A one-on-one match.
The top-voted contestant
will now be revealed.
Who will it be?
I don't want people to know my answer.
I bet it'd feel good to be picked.
I guess so.
Team Australia's
Eddie Williams.
No surprises there!
No!
I mean, how are you
supposed to go up against him?
Even two-on-one wouldn't cut it.
That's a good photo though, Eddie.
You look angry!
-Eddie.
Eddie.
How are you supposed to beat him?
He's an absolute unit.
He's basically Godzilla.
I don't think anyone can top Eddie
when it comes to strength.
So please don't pair me up with him.
You're the monster.
-"Monster."
-Godzilla.
"Godzilla."
He just swore again.
Why is everyone so scared of him?
I don't get it.
There's no one
I want to avoid in a one-on-one.
I'd gladly go up against anyone.
A game will now begin
that will allow you to gauge
the strength of other contestants.
-Gauge the strength, huh?
-The game is called
one-on-one hand wrestling.
Hand wrestle? Like that?
-Arm wrestling.
-Bro, I told you.
-Arm wrestle?
Hand wrestling
is a game of push and pull
between clasped hands.
You must force your opponent
to lift a foot
or fall over in order to win.
The matchups have been set
based on the votes
of the pre-quest survey.
What, no one wants to fight me?
But I'm really intimidating!
I'm kind of annoyed no one voted for me.
I guess this means I got some votes then.
Getting no votes hurts, man.
First up are Eddie Williams
of Team Australia…
Eddie, Eddie.
…and Kim Min-jae
-of Team Republic of Korea.
-This is anyone's game, Min-jae.
Anything could happen.
-Let's go!
-Let's go.
This will be an epic showdown.
I don't think Eddie will budge at all.
He'll be rock solid.
You've got to be strategic.
-Go, Min-jae!
-Small, quick movements, okay?
Wait.
Just one grip, and he's like, "Oh!"
I grabbed his hand,
and it was as big as a pot lid.
That's when I realized
that he's just built differently.
Still, as a Cheonhajangsa champion,
I was feeling good about my chances.
He looks like Eddie gave birth to him.
Good luck.
Go get it.
Ready…
Go, Eddie!
Eddie almost lifted his foot.
That was close.
I think you'll win this, Min-jae.
Show him what you've got, Min-jae!
Eddie Williams wins.
Good effort, Min-jae!
-Incredible.
-That was amazing.
Conserve your energy.
Good effort. Good try.
Damn, I can't beat that guy.
Orkhonbayar Bayarsaikhan of Team Mongolia
will be facing off against
Yoshio Itoi of Team Japan.
Check out those cannonball shoulders.
He's jacked and has huge shoulders.
Wow, he's impressive for sure.
He looks insanely strong.
Ready…
Orkhonbayar Bayarsaikhan wins.
He just…
Straight up pulled him down.
That was a bad matchup.
Strong!
Eddie Williams of Team Australia
-Come on, Eddie.
-and Orkhonbayar Bayarsaikhan
of Team Mongolia.
Look at their weight difference.
-There must be a 70 kg difference.
-Orkhonbayar looks small next to him.
Don't injure yourself.
Ready…
-No one even comes close.
-He's too strong.
He's practically cemented to the floor.
Eddie Williams of Team Australia wins.
Yeah, good game, guys.
He's a total beast.
Group B.
Robert Whittaker of Team Australia
will be facing off against
Amotti of Team Republic of Korea.
Amotti!
Come on, Amotti. Show them!
If I beat him, that means
-I've beaten a UFC fighter, right?
-Absolutely.
Whittaker's got this, hands down.
My bet's on Whittaker.
I'd only ever seen Whittaker on TV,
so I was thrilled I got to wrestle him.
But of course I doubted
that I'd beat a UFC fighter like him
in a strength contest.
Whittaker's going to
wipe the floor with him.
Yes, I'll win. For sure.
For sure.
Ready…
Amotti wins.
Nice, he beat a UFC champion.
Whittaker went in, and he went like this.
You know what? He's a wily guy.
He surprised me.
Little wily bugger.
Whittaker, you ask?
Well, I took him down with one hand.
Enkh-Orgil Baatarkhuu of Team Mongolia
and Yushin Okami of Team Japan.
You can't lose this.
Your opponent is small.
There's no way you'd lose.
It's UFC versus UFC.
He's going up against a big guy.
Look at the weight class difference.
You never know because
that Mongolian man is pretty tenacious.
He's a total wild card.
Ready…
Okami's base is really good.
Yeah, he's got it nice and low.
Really nice, wide stance.
They're both so strong.
Strength alone won't cut it.
They're too neck and neck.
We were pretty evenly matched.
I had a good shot at winning this.
Good, yeah. Pull, Okami!
This is a fun one.
This is a really fun one.
It's funny because
there's so much size difference,
-but their strengths match.
-Yeah.
Three hours!
Such an even battle.
Yushin Okami wins.
Amotti of Team Republic of Korea
will be facing off against
Yushin Okami of Team Japan.
Amotti's ripped.
-He is, right?
-He looks amazing.
-Who?
-Amotti.
No, come on. Cut the Amotti fan club.
Yushin's our guy.
We're not here
for an Amotti lovefest, okay?
Go take down your second UFC fighter.
Let's go, Yushin.
Let's go, Amotti.
What's going on with the hands there?
Sorry.
Red card!
This isn't good.
No losing your grip, man!
Okay.
You punched me once,
so I'll punch you once.
No, no.
He wanted to punch him back?
Ready…
Yushin Okami of Team Japan wins.
Even though it was for recreation,
I still wanted to beat Eddie
so it wouldn't hurt our confidence
in the real competition.
I knew he still had technique, so I…
He pulled him so effortlessly.
He's strong.
Just kind of win.
I didn't give him enough time
to even think about a strategy.
He can't just pick him up like that.
That was over in a split second.
How is that possible?
It was like an adult with a toddler.
Eddie Williams of Team Australia
has won the final round.
That's just insane.
I was reminded once again
how strong he was,
both physically and mentally.
-Everyone was right.
-Surely.
You were the scariest.
So don't ever doubt the Strongman.
We can be strong, and we can be fit.
A game will now begin
that will allow you to gauge
the strength of other contestants.
Another game.
The game is called the vertical jump.
Vertical jump?
A vertical jump's basically
a Sargent jump.
This is Sung-bin's wheelhouse, isn't it?
This is Sung-bin's game.
Why vertical? Make it horizontal.
You are allowed
two attempts at each height.
Two attempts.
Each country will now select
one representative for the game.
Come on, this is a no-brainer.
Mark my words.
There's nobody here
who can jump better than Sung-bin.
YUN SUNG-BIN
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM SKELETON RACER
This is Sung-bin's time to shine.
Who will play?
We pick one.
Me or you?
Me or Eloni.
Eloni, you're taller, bro.
Eloni, that would be you, wouldn't it?
Wouldn't that be Eloni?
Because of the height.
It makes a big difference.
I trained a lot of jumps too
for this competition.
Eloni has the height advantage as well.
It's got to be you.
It'd take you less effort
because you're tall.
I'm the tallest on the team,
and being a basketball player,
I was the only one who could jump high.
We have Katsumi.
-Should I do it?
-You can do it.
You jump when you swim, right?
Yeah, into the pool.
I want to do my best
and really show off my charm.
Contestants of the vertical jump,
please come to the center.
He's the shortest.
Coming in first as the shortest
would be legendary.
Everyone there can jump.
Contestants of the vertical jump.
Eloni Vunakece of Team Australia.
Katsumi Nakamura of Team Japan.
Yun Sung-bin of Team Republic of Korea.
Dulguun Enkhbat of Team Mongolia.
I bet the rugby guy can jump.
Rugby players can jump.
He could be really explosive.
I'm not sure about the swimmer.
I'm more worried
about the basketball player.
I'm keen to see Sung-bin jump in person.
Yeah, I'm actually keen too.
The 300 cm vertical jump.
300 cm?
He won't lose this, will he?
Eloni literally just does this for fun.
-He jumps and tries to reach stuff.
-Yeah.
I know, that's why I sent him on this.
Easy money, G!
Is this a joke?
You'll be fine!
You can do it.
Use your arm.
Yeah! Good jump!
You can go higher.
No way!
What just happened?
Yeah! I love watching you jump, bro.
-He's so floaty, eh?
-He's so floaty.
Go! You got this!
Yeah!
320 cm.
320?
This will be tough.
This is going to weed out the pack.
Easy money, Lons.
Full jump, nice touch.
Just don't miss it.
Nah, he's got it.
That was unexpected.
-One more.
-You're gonna have to give it a bit more.
Oh, shirt off!
It works better when you do it like this.
-Is that really necessary?
-You miss this, and you're done!
-Give it a bit more, G!
-Let's go, bro!
I'm just gonna hit it
with everything I've got
and hopefully, that's enough.
Let's go, bro.
I touched it!
He touched it! Yeah, he did touch it.
-Yeah! Come on!
-Yes!
See? Take the shirt off,
and it works better!
I couldn't believe someone with his build
could jump like that.
He was like a whole different species.
He really is something.
This is insane.
You can do it!
-You can do it.
-You can do it!
There's no way I can do this.
That's all right.
Look, he's nowhere near it.
He's off by at least 20 cm.
Take your shirt off.
Shirt off, it makes it better.
There we go!
-Go get it, Katsumi!
-Let's go!
I really wanted to crush this.
I knew I had the leg strength to do it.
He did go higher.
-He did go higher.
-It was higher.
Yeah, 320 cm was…
I thought I might make it,
but it was just too high.
It was out of my reach
by just a few centimeters.
Damn.
What the hell? It's so high up.
Come on, Sung-bin.
Show us, Yun Sung-bin!
This is too much, even for Sung-bin.
He'll totally hit that.
Oh my gosh!
That jump was insane.
You can do it!
Rip it off, bro!
So good!
-Show us!
-Show us, Sung-bin!
Come on, Sung-bin! Show us you can do it!
He'll do it. I reckon he got it.
That really is so high.
So close!
I thought I could reach it,
but I couldn't.
He still made it up
to the center of the blue bars.
-Adjusting for height, he hit it.
-Yeah, with the 30 cm height difference.
Mongolia!
-He'll make it.
-Yeah, he can do this.
It looked totally doable.
Just a bit more!
Go again. Go full reach.
Oh, shit.
Let's go!
See, eh?
You take your shirt off,
it works every time. See?
I thought I'd own this.
I'm super bummed.
In first place is
Eloni Vunakece of Team Australia.
Yes!
That's our boy!
Let's go!
That's two straight wins for Australia.
-They're first in everything, no?
-They are.
-Right?
-Yes.
Out of the four countries remaining,
it's painfully obvious
that Australia's the biggest threat.
We can't beat them.
It's impossible.
I am the highest jumper
in all of the Asian nations.
Asia's highest jumper, Eloni Vunakece.
We will now begin
the fourth quest of Physical: Asia.
Let's go!
-All righty.
-Come on!
Contestants,
please make your way into the arena.
Here we go. Here we go!
-Let's do this!
-All right!
Last 30 seconds of your life!
Pace yourself! Come on!
Subtitle translation by: Jee Butcher